{"data": [{"type": "sign", "id": "sign_1", "question": "signsign_1", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "172", "correct": "false", "text": "Hidden intersection ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "172", "correct": "true", "text": "Winding road ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "172", "correct": "false", "text": "Road slippery when wet"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "172", "correct": "false", "text": "Narrow road ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_2", "question": "signsign_2", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "173", "correct": "false", "text": "Factory, slow down"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "173", "correct": "true", "text": "Bump or uneven pavement"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "173", "correct": "false", "text": "Construction zone"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "173", "correct": "false", "text": "Bridge or viaduct"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_3", "question": "signsign_3", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "174", "correct": "false", "text": "You are approaching a four-way intersection"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "174", "correct": "false", "text": "You are approaching a pedestrian crosswalk"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "174", "correct": "false", "text": "You are approaching a hospital zone"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "174", "correct": "true", "text": "You are approaching a railroad crossing"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_4", "question": "signsign_4", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "175", "correct": "true", "text": "Divided highway ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "175", "correct": "false", "text": "Divided highway ends"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "175", "correct": "false", "text": "Narrow bridge ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "175", "correct": "false", "text": "Road under construction"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_5", "question": "signsign_5", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "176", "correct": "false", "text": "Beware of a hidden intersection"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "176", "correct": "true", "text": "Intersection ahead, the arrow shows which direction of traffic has the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "176", "correct": "false", "text": "Traffic going in the direction of the arrow does not have the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "176", "correct": "false", "text": "Railway crossing ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_6", "question": "signsign_6", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "177", "correct": "false", "text": "Sign indicates traffic going in the direction of the arrow have the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "177", "correct": "false", "text": "Danger, the road ahead ends"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "177", "correct": "true", "text": "Sharp turn on the road in the direction of the arrow; drive with caution"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "177", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not turn right"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_7", "question": "signsign_7", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "178", "correct": "false", "text": "Parking for trucks ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "178", "correct": "false", "text": "No trucks are permitted beyond this sign"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "178", "correct": "false", "text": "Bumpy road ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "178", "correct": "true", "text": "The sign warns of a steep hill ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_8", "question": "signsign_8", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "179", "correct": "true", "text": "Deer cross regularly; drive with caution"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "179", "correct": "false", "text": "Destination board indicating a zoo"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "179", "correct": "false", "text": "No standing between signs"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "179", "correct": "false", "text": "None of the above"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_9", "question": "signsign_9", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "180", "correct": "true", "text": "Road ahead slippery when wet"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "180", "correct": "false", "text": "Bumpy road ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "180", "correct": "false", "text": "Railway crossing ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "180", "correct": "false", "text": "Winding road ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_10", "question": "signsign_10", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "181", "correct": "false", "text": "Divided highway begins ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "181", "correct": "false", "text": "Narrow bridge ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "181", "correct": "true", "text": "Divided highway ends ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "181", "correct": "false", "text": "Winding road ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_11", "question": "signsign_11", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "182", "correct": "false", "text": "No truck allowed"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "182", "correct": "true", "text": "Truck entrance on the right side ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "182", "correct": "false", "text": "Slow down for trucks"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "182", "correct": "false", "text": "Truck route"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_12", "question": "signsign_12", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "183", "correct": "false", "text": "Road is blocked ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "183", "correct": "true", "text": "Narrow bridge ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "183", "correct": "false", "text": "Pedestrian crossing ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "183", "correct": "false", "text": "This sign means only local traffic allowed"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_13", "question": "signsign_13", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "184", "correct": "false", "text": "No passing allowed"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "184", "correct": "false", "text": "Drive with caution when passing a vehicle"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "184", "correct": "true", "text": "Share the road with oncoming traffic"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "184", "correct": "false", "text": "The road is divided by a traffic island"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_14", "question": "signsign_14", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "185", "correct": "true", "text": "Traffic signals ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "185", "correct": "false", "text": "Stop sign 150 meters (500 feet) ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "185", "correct": "false", "text": "Bump 125 meters (400 feet) ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "185", "correct": "false", "text": "Railroad crossing ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_15", "question": "signsign_15", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "186", "correct": "false", "text": "You must not make a right turn"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "186", "correct": "false", "text": "You are approaching traffic signal lights"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "186", "correct": "true", "text": "You are approaching a stop sign"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "186", "correct": "false", "text": "You must not make a left turn"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_16", "question": "signsign_16", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "187", "correct": "false", "text": "Road ahead is blocked"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "187", "correct": "false", "text": "You must make a right at the next intersection"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "187", "correct": "true", "text": "Hidden intersection ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "187", "correct": "false", "text": "None of the above"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_17", "question": "signsign_17", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "188", "correct": "false", "text": "Right lane exits"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "188", "correct": "true", "text": "Slight bend or curve in the road ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "188", "correct": "false", "text": "You must make a right turn"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "188", "correct": "false", "text": "U-Turns permitted"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_18", "question": "signsign_18", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "189", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not enter"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "189", "correct": "false", "text": "Traffic lights ahead; you have the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "189", "correct": "false", "text": "The action within the green circle is prohibited"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "189", "correct": "true", "text": "Permissive sign"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_19", "question": "signsign_19", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "190", "correct": "true", "text": "This parking space is restricted for vehicles displaying a valid handicap Access Parking Permit"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "190", "correct": "false", "text": "Only wheelchairs can be parked here"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "190", "correct": "false", "text": "No parking allowed"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "190", "correct": "false", "text": "Sign indicates driver's who have an Access Parking Permit may not park here"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_20", "question": "signsign_20", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "191", "correct": "false", "text": "No entry into intersection"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "191", "correct": "true", "text": "No stopping at any time between signs"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "191", "correct": "false", "text": "Vehicles approaching from the angle shown must stop"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "191", "correct": "false", "text": "Stop not needed for stop signs in directions of arrows."}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_21", "question": "signsign_21", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "192", "correct": "true", "text": "No left turn during times indicated; all other times permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "192", "correct": "false", "text": "No left turn any time"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "192", "correct": "false", "text": "No right turn during times indicated; all other times permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "192", "correct": "false", "text": "No right turn any time"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_22", "question": "signsign_22", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "193", "correct": "true", "text": "Do not drive through intersection"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "193", "correct": "false", "text": "The road is blocked beyond the sign"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "193", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not enter"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "193", "correct": "false", "text": "Stop immediately"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_23", "question": "signsign_23", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "194", "correct": "false", "text": "Bridge or viaduct ahead; proceed with caution"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "194", "correct": "false", "text": "Route ahead is for trucks only"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "194", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not enter unless local traffic"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "194", "correct": "true", "text": "Prohibited sign"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_24", "question": "signsign_24", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "197", "correct": "false", "text": "Beware of passing vehicles"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "197", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not enter"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "197", "correct": "true", "text": "No passing allowed at any time"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "197", "correct": "false", "text": "You are approaching steep hill"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_25", "question": "signsign_25", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "198", "correct": "false", "text": "No buses allowed on specified lane during posted times"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "198", "correct": "false", "text": "No stopping within the times"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "198", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not enter between the times"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "198", "correct": "true", "text": "This lane is reserved for specific types of and/or a specific amount of passengers in a vehicle"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_26", "question": "signsign_26", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "200", "correct": "false", "text": "No right turns permitted on this street"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "200", "correct": "false", "text": "Right turns are permitted when the light is red"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "200", "correct": "false", "text": "On red lights you must stop and check if it is safe before making a right turn"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "200", "correct": "true", "text": "Right turns are not permitted when the light is red"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_27", "question": "signsign_27", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "202", "correct": "false", "text": "You must make a right turn only"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "202", "correct": "true", "text": "You must not make a left turn"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "202", "correct": "false", "text": "Hidden intersection ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "202", "correct": "false", "text": "You are approaching a traffic island"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_28", "question": "signsign_28", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "203", "correct": "true", "text": "The speed limit is 50 km/h"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "203", "correct": "false", "text": "Speed limit of 50 km/h ends"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "203", "correct": "false", "text": "Speed limit of 50 km/h begins"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "203", "correct": "false", "text": "A and C is correct"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_29", "question": "signsign_29", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "204", "correct": "true", "text": "School zone, drive 30km/h when lights are flashing"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "204", "correct": "false", "text": "Maximum 30km/h beyond this point"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "204", "correct": "false", "text": "Pedestrian crossing ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "204", "correct": "false", "text": "None of the above"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_30", "question": "signsign_30", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "205", "correct": "true", "text": "No right turns permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "205", "correct": "false", "text": "No left turns permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "205", "correct": "false", "text": "You may right turn if the light is green"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "205", "correct": "false", "text": "You may right turn if the light is yellow"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_31", "question": "signsign_31", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "206", "correct": "false", "text": "You have the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "206", "correct": "false", "text": "Railway crossing ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "206", "correct": "true", "text": "You must give the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "206", "correct": "false", "text": "School area ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_32", "question": "signsign_32", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "207", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not enter unless local traffic"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "207", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not pass"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "207", "correct": "true", "text": "Do not enter"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "207", "correct": "false", "text": "Traffic circle ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_33", "question": "signsign_33", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "208", "correct": "true", "text": "Parking is only permitted between the signs at the times shown; 30 mins allowed"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "208", "correct": "false", "text": "Parking is permitted for 30mins on any day"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "208", "correct": "false", "text": "Parking is not allowed at any time"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "208", "correct": "false", "text": "None of the above"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_34", "question": "signsign_34", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "209", "correct": "true", "text": "No pedestrians allowed on roadway"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "209", "correct": "false", "text": "Beware of pedestrian on the road"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "209", "correct": "false", "text": "Road slippery when wet"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "209", "correct": "false", "text": "No standing"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_35", "question": "signsign_35", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "210", "correct": "false", "text": "Road slippery when wet"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "210", "correct": "false", "text": "No left turn permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "210", "correct": "false", "text": "No right turn permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "210", "correct": "true", "text": "You must not make a \"U\" turn"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_36", "question": "signsign_36", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "211", "correct": "false", "text": "No standing between signs"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "211", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not block intersection"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "211", "correct": "true", "text": "No parking allowed between signs"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "211", "correct": "false", "text": "Parking is available to the left and right of the sign"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_37", "question": "signsign_37", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "212", "correct": "false", "text": "Approaching railroad crossing; slow down and prepare to stop"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "212", "correct": "true", "text": "Approaching pedestrian cross walk; slow down and prepare to stop and yield to the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "212", "correct": "false", "text": "Approaching intersection; slow down and prepare to stop"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "212", "correct": "false", "text": "No pedestrians allowed on the road"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_38", "question": "signsign_38", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "214", "correct": "true", "text": "You must yield to the bus once it has signalled its intent to return to lane"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "214", "correct": "false", "text": "You may pass the bus if it is safe"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "214", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not pass buses"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "214", "correct": "false", "text": "Make sure you signal before making a t"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_39", "question": "signsign_39", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "215", "correct": "true", "text": "No bicycles permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "215", "correct": "false", "text": "Bikes are permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "215", "correct": "false", "text": "Share the road with bicyclist"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "215", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not leave bicycles unattended in this area"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_40", "question": "signsign_40", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "216", "correct": "false", "text": "Railroad crossing ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "216", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not enter"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "216", "correct": "false", "text": "Pedestrian crossing ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "216", "correct": "true", "text": "Vehicles cannot cross/change lanes"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_41", "question": "signsign_41", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "217", "correct": "false", "text": "I am turning right"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "217", "correct": "true", "text": "I am turning left"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "217", "correct": "false", "text": "I am slowing or stopping"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "217", "correct": "false", "text": "None of the above"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_42", "question": "signsign_42", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "218", "correct": "true", "text": "Lane usage sign meaning right turn only"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "218", "correct": "false", "text": "The road ahead curves to the right"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "218", "correct": "false", "text": "The road ahead curves to the left"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "218", "correct": "false", "text": "Lane usage sign permitting all turns"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_43", "question": "signsign_43", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "219", "correct": "false", "text": "Playground zone sign for students"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "219", "correct": "false", "text": "Children playing in residential area"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "219", "correct": "true", "text": "School zone sign"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "219", "correct": "false", "text": "Bus stop ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_44", "question": "signsign_44", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "220", "correct": "false", "text": "You might make a left turn"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "220", "correct": "false", "text": "You must go straight"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "220", "correct": "false", "text": "You cannot turn right"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "220", "correct": "true", "text": "Traffic is permitted only in the direction of the sign"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_45", "question": "signsign_45", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "221", "correct": "true", "text": "This sign means there is a two-way shared left turn lane"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "221", "correct": "false", "text": "This sign means there is a left or right turn lane"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "221", "correct": "false", "text": "This sign means there is a two-way right turn lane"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "221", "correct": "false", "text": "Beware of slippery roads"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_46", "question": "signsign_46", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "222", "correct": "true", "text": "Stop at all times"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "222", "correct": "false", "text": "Stop only if other vehicles are approaching"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "222", "correct": "false", "text": "Stop sign 150 meters"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "222", "correct": "false", "text": "Stop sign 125 meters"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_47", "question": "signsign_47", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "223", "correct": "false", "text": "I am turning left"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "223", "correct": "false", "text": "I am turning right"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "223", "correct": "true", "text": "I am slowing or stopping"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "223", "correct": "false", "text": "No passing allowed"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_48", "question": "signsign_48", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "224", "correct": "true", "text": "New driver"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "224", "correct": "false", "text": "New born baby on broad"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "224", "correct": "false", "text": "Parking is permitted"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "224", "correct": "false", "text": "No parking is permitted"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_49", "question": "signsign_49", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "225", "correct": "true", "text": "This sign shows wheelchair accessible facilities"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "225", "correct": "false", "text": "No standing allowed"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "225", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not park here"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "225", "correct": "false", "text": "Beware of low speed vehicles"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_50", "question": "signsign_50", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "226", "correct": "true", "text": "I am turning right"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "226", "correct": "false", "text": "I am turning left"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "226", "correct": "false", "text": "I am slowing or stopping"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "226", "correct": "false", "text": "None of the above"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_51", "question": "signsign_51", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "227", "correct": "false", "text": "Beware of children playing"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "227", "correct": "true", "text": "Highway work operations ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "227", "correct": "false", "text": "Do not block pedestrian crossing"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "227", "correct": "false", "text": "Construction sign - slow down - obey fragments decisions"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_52", "question": "signsign_52", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "229", "correct": "false", "text": "Watch out for children passing"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "229", "correct": "false", "text": "Beware of pedestrians crossing the road"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "229", "correct": "true", "text": "Traffic control person ahead, drive slowly and watch for instructions"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "229", "correct": "false", "text": "School bus zone"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_53", "question": "signsign_53", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "231", "correct": "true", "text": "Slow moving vehicle ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "231", "correct": "false", "text": "You have the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "231", "correct": "false", "text": "Yield to the right-of-way"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "231", "correct": "false", "text": "Construction site ahead"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_54", "question": "signsign_54", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "301", "correct": "true", "text": "Pass to right of traffic island"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "301", "correct": "false", "text": "Road turns right then left"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "301", "correct": "false", "text": "Winding road ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "301", "correct": "false", "text": "Pass other traffic on the right"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_55", "question": "signsign_55", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "303", "correct": "false", "text": "Divided highway ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "303", "correct": "false", "text": "You are approaching a one-way street"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "303", "correct": "false", "text": "Hidden intersection ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "303", "correct": "true", "text": "Pavement narrows"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_56", "question": "signsign_56", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "304", "correct": "true", "text": "Destination board"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "304", "correct": "false", "text": "School zone - watch for children playing"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "304", "correct": "false", "text": "Provincial park"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "304", "correct": "false", "text": "Pedestrian control sign meaning no active games"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_57", "question": "signsign_57", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "305", "correct": "false", "text": "X intersection for school vehicles"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "305", "correct": "false", "text": "School crosswalk sign"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "305", "correct": "false", "text": "Caution - school bus crossing"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "305", "correct": "true", "text": "Regulatory sign"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_58", "question": "signsign_58", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "306", "correct": "false", "text": "Stop sign"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "306", "correct": "false", "text": "Yield sign"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "306", "correct": "false", "text": "Slow moving vehicle"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "306", "correct": "true", "text": "School bus stop arm"}]}, {"type": "sign", "id": "sign_59", "question": "signsign_59", "options": [{"option_id": "option_1", "question_id": "307", "correct": "false", "text": "Maximum speed 50 km/h (30 miles) from this sign to the next"}, {"option_id": "option_2", "question_id": "307", "correct": "false", "text": "Speed limit for rural school zone"}, {"option_id": "option_3", "question_id": "307", "correct": "false", "text": "End of 50 km/h (30 miles) ahead"}, {"option_id": "option_4", "question_id": "307", "correct": "true", "text": "Maximum speed 50 km/h (30 miles) ahead"}]}]}